Erickson Eaton

55 Lanark Rd Boston, MA 02135

781-248-4583 • ericksoneaton7@gmail.com

MACHINE LEARNING, DATA SCIENCE, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING OR RELATED AREA PYTHON, R, SQL, NODE.JS, DJANGO

Valuable blend of education and practical experience applying a valuable range of skills necessary to become an effective contributor in the above-referenced positions. Collaborative worker and skilled analytical problem solver. Valuable professional experience utilizing skills in design, testing, analysis, and solutions-based processes in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment. History of working efficiently, prioritizing responsibilities and workflow, and supporting management.

EDUCATION

University of Massachusetts - Lowell, MA

Bachelor of Science, Mathematics (August 2020)

- Concentration: **Probability and Statistics**
- Minor: Economics
- Major GPA: 3.6; overall GPA: 3.4
- Senior Project: General Linear Models
- Related coursework:
 - Experimental Design randomized block designs, randomization, blocking, matching, analysis of variance and covariance, control of extraneous variables
 - Linear Statistics Modeling and Regression (R)
 - Machine Learning (Python)
 - Mathematical Statistics I & II
 - Applied Statistics (using Minitab)
 - Mathematical Modeling
- Math Tutor (paid position, all levels)

RELATED EXPERIENCE

EvenKeel Performance Insoles - Brookline, MA

Software Engineer (2018-2022)

- Effectively built a Python machine learning program for automatically creating custom insoles from images, leveraging modern tools such as Convolutional Neural Networks, Tensorflow, and Keras.
- Efficiently utilized libraries such as Numpy and Pandas for analyzing and organizing incoming image data.
- Conducted testing on web application, analyzed results, and submitted observations to development team.
- Developed and collaborated with team members to design an automatic invoicing system using Node.js, Firebase, and Google Cloud Functions.
- Produced additional image functionality for iOS app with Swift.

Shift4 - Remote

Software Engineer II- Payments Development (November 2021- February 2022)

- Wrote and ran software testing on Linux systems for handling credit card processing.
- Maintained Python and PostgreSQL code and updated documentation.

OTHER EMPLOYMENT

Frank J. Santopietro D.P.M. - Brookline, MA

Office Manager (2018)

 Oversaw appointment scheduling and responded to client billing questions as well as other business and client information requests.

Mass Wholesale Tire - Revere, MA

Warehouse Assistant (2013-2017)

• Worked with inventory movement, transport, and storage areas during high school and into college years.

CERTIFICATIONS

TensorFlow Developer Certificate – Google